Finding Aid for Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (University of Michigan) Records, 1909-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Central Topical Files, 1929-2003
  - 1937-1999, 1980-1991
    - Purchasing
      - Performance Review of University Stores by Plante and Moran, 1981-1982 (Box 131)
    - Rackham Graduate School
      - Rackham Funds, 1972-1983 (Box 131)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971-1991 (Box 132)
    - Radrick, Miscellaneous, 1986-1991; 2 folders (Box 132)
    - Regents
      - Bylaws, 1972-1991 (Box 132)
      - Meetings-Open/Closed, Attorney General Opinion, 1969-1977 (Box 132)
      - Miscellaneous, 1978-1991; 3 folders (Box 132)
    - Research
      - Excellence Fund, 1986-1988 (Box 132)
      - Freedom of Information Act Letters, 1987-1989 (Box 132)
      - High Technology, 1980-1988 (Box 132)
      - Vice President Search, 1984-1985 (Box 132)
    - Safety
      - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 132)
      - Campus Police Force and Parking Operations. Bureau, 1988-1991 (Box 133)
      - Radiation Control Service, 1985-1991; 2 folders (Box 133)
      - Task Force on Safety and Security, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 133)
    - Salary Disclosure, 1979-1991 (Box 133)
    - Security
      - Miscellaneous, 1988-1991 (Box 133)
      - ID Cards, 1975-1990 (Box 133)
    - Senate Assembly Advisory Committee on Financial Affairs
      - Agendas and Minutes, 1976-1987; 4 folders (Box 133)
    - Senate Assembly Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1977-1991; 2 folders (Box 134)
    - Service Awards Dinner, 1976-1991 (Box 134)
    - Speeches
      - Farris W. Womack Speeches, 1989-1996; 6 folders (Box 134)
        [see also Box 142]
      - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 134)
    - Staff Benefits
      - Blue Cross-Blue Shield, 1972-1988 (Box 135)
      - Dependent Care, 1986-1991 (Box 135)
      - Disability, 1985-1991 (Box 135)
      - Early Retirement, 1972-1984 (Box 135)
      - Flexible Benefits, 1973-1983 (Box 135)
      - Flexible/Modular, 1987-1991 (Box 135)
      - Group Life Insurance, 1950-1991 (Box 135)
      - Health Care Cost Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 135)
      - Health Care Options, 1984-1991 (Box 135)
      - Health Insurance Rates, 1973-1991 (Box 135)
      - Individual Benefit Statement, 1974-1976; 1980; 1986 (Box 135)
      - Legislation
        - 1974-1988 (Box 135)
        - 1989-1991 (Box 136)
      - Long Term Disability, 1973-1983; 2 folders (Box 136)
      - Major Medical, 1970-1991 (Box 136)
      - Medical Reimbursements, 1975-1990 (Box 136)
      - Retirement
        - General, 1973-1991; 3 folders (Box 136)
        - Equal Benefits for Women, 1972-1976; 2 folders (Box 136)
        - Furlough, 1983-1984 (Box 136)
        - Older Faculty, 1971-1988 (Box 136)
        - Supplemental Benefits, 1975; 1977; 1979; 1985-1988 (Box 136)
        - Taxation of Pension, 1970; 1973-1974; 1978; 1986 (Box 137)
        - TIAA/CREF, 1985-1991; 2 folders (Box 137)
          [see also Boxes 75 and 142]
      - TITLE IX Sex Discrimination, EEOC, 1973-1975; 1977-1981; 1984 (Box 137)
      - Wellness Programs, 1987-1991 (Box 137)
      - Miscellaneous, 1983-1991; 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Standard and Poor Rating Visit, October 27, 1989 (Box 137)
    - Student Publications, Board for, 1986-1989 (Box 137)
    - Sugar Island
      - Easement for Road (W. Hamilton), 1974-1978 (Box 137)
      - Lake Superior State College, 1972-1975 (Box 137)
    - Taxes
      - Tax Exemption and Miscellaneous, 1968-1991 (Box 137)
      - Withholding for Graduate Students Tuition Remission, 1982-1985; 1988-1989 (Box 138)
    - Television
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1973; 1975; 1985; 1987-1990 (Box 138)
      - Instructional Television Fixed Service (ITFS), 1984-1985; 1989 (Box 138)
    - Telecommunications
      - Emergency Telephone Service, 1985-1988; 1990 (Box 138)
      - New Telephone System
        - 1982-1990, 6 folders (Box 138)
    - Telecommunications Consultant (STC), 1983-1984 (Box 139)
    - Tennessee, University of, 1989-1991 (Box 139)
    - Transportation, 1986-1991 (Box 139)
    - Travel and Expense Reimbursement, 1989-1991; 2 folders (Box 139)
    - University Events, Office of, 1989-1991 (Box 139)
    - Utilities, 1988-1991 (Box 139)
    - Visitors, 1989-1991 (Box 139)
    - W-Miscellaneous, 1975-1978; 1983-1988; 1990 (Box 139)
    - Washtenaw Community College, 1984-1985 (Box 139)
    - Washtenaw County, Miscellaneous, 1970-1991 (Box 139)
    - Waste Recycling, 1988-1991 (Box 139)
    - Weiner, Kenneth, 1989 (Box 139)
    - Y, Z-Miscellaneous, 1974-1976
  - 1951-1997, 1982-1997
    The 1951-1997 Topical File subseries, accessioned in 2003, totals just 3 linear feet of alphabetically arranged subject files. These records cover the years 1951-1997, although the bulk of the material dates between 1982 and 1997. There is considerable overlap with prior accessions so an attempt has been made to provide cross-references to related documentation in other parts of the record group when necessary. Topics documented in these files include the Business and Finance Lead Team, part of the university's M-Quality initiative to improve quality in higher education; summaries of work accomplished by various departments reporting to the vice president in the form of Reports to the President and a report to the Board of Regents, "Reflections: 1988-1993"; the university's involvement in the development of a high technology research park in Ann Arbor; and broader financial and personnel issues.
    - Budget
      - 1994-1995 (Box 140)
        [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2023 ]
      - 1995-1996 (Box 140)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 140)
    - Business and Finance Lead Team
      - 1992 (Box 140)
      - 1993, 3 folders (Box 140)
      - 1994, 2 folders (Box 140)
      - 1995, 2 folders (Box 140)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 140)
    - Capital Outlay-Miscellaneous, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 140)
      [see also Boxes 69 and 94]
    - Capital Outlay Team, 1988-1994 (Box 140)
    - CIESIN (Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network): Finance Standing Committee, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 141)
    - Compensation-Study (Compensation Program Task Force), 1988 (Box 141)
      [see also Boxes 95 and 96]
    - Encyclopedic Survey Update, 1978 (Box 141)
    - Information Technology Division (ITD)
      - January-August 1992 (Box 141)
      - September-December 1992 (Box 141)
      - 1993 (Box 141)
      - 1994 (Box 141)
      - 1995, 2 folders (Box 141)
      - 1996 (Box 141)
    - Insurance: Veritas Insurance Corporation
      [see also Box 111]
      - January-June 1992, 2 folders (Box 141)
      - July-October 1992 (Box 141)
    - Michigan, State of: Miscellaneous
      [see also Box 125]
      - 1992-1993 (Box 141)
      - 1994 (Box 141)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 141)
    - Michigan Partnership for New Education (MPNE), 1989-1996 (Box 141)
    - Personnel: Human Resource Review Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 141)
    - President's Report
      (previous reports located in Bentley stacks)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 141)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 141)
    - Provost Advisory Committee on Excellence (PACE), 1991 (Box 142)
    - "Reflections: 1988-1993", 1994 (Box 142)
      (overview of accomplishments)
    - Research: Miscellaneous
      - 1994 (Box 142)
      - 1995 (Box 142)
    - Research Park-Ann Arbor (Ann Arbor Technology Park)
      - Richard Wood, 1982-1990; 2 folders (Box 142)
      - Wood agreement, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 142)
    - Speeches: Farris W. Womack Speeches
      [see also Box 134]
      - May-June 1990, 2 folders (Box 142)
      - August-November 1990 (Box 142)
      - 1991 (Box 142)
      - 1992 (Box 142)
    - Staff Benefits: TIAA-CREF
      [see also Boxes 75 and 137]
      - Cash option, 1971-1972 (Box 142)
      - History, 1951-1963 (Box 142)
      - Regents Communication, 1952-1971 (Box 142)
  - 1957-2003, 1992-2002
    The Central Topical Files, 1957-2003, date primarily from the period between when Farris Womack was named the first Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer in 1993, through Robert Kasdin's tenure in the position, which ended in 2002. As with previous accessions, however, this one also contains some older information in files that predated but were maintained during the main time frame.
    - Academic Affairs, Office of, 1996-1997 (Box 160)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2026 ]
    - Account Statements, miscellaneous, 1997-1999 (Box 160)
    - Affirmative Action -- Martin Luther King, Jr. Day, 1992-1994; 3 folders (Box 160)
    - Ann Arbor / University Relations, 1992-1998; 5 folders (Box 160)
    - Athletics, 1992-1995 (Box 160)
    - Athletics -- News Clippings, 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 160)
    - Audit
      - Misc., 1993-1995 (Box 161)
      - Auditor General
        - Dearborn, 1984-1990 (Box 161)
        - Flint, 1985-1989 (Box 161)
        - General Fund, 1979-1994; 2 folders (Box 161)
      - Outside Auditors
        - 1996-1998, 7 folders (Box 161)
        - 1992-1995, 4 folders (Box 162)
      - PricewaterhouseCoopers, 1999; 5 folders (Box 162)
      - Reports to Regents, 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Banks, misc., 1992-1995 (Box 163)
    - Big Ten
      - Miscellaneous, 1995-1998; 6 folders (Box 163)
      - Athletics, 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 163)
    - Broadcasting and Media Services, 1996-2000; 2 folders (Box 163)
    - Budget
      - 1997-2000, 4 folders (Box 164)
      - CFO area, 1998-1999; 3 folders (Box 164)
      - RCM / VCM, 1994-1998; 3 folders (Box 164)
      - Regents Communications, 1989-1999; 3 folders (Box 164)
      - Year End Closing and Fiscal Reports, 1992-1995 (Box 165)
    - Business Administration, miscellaneous, 1989-1995 (Box 165)
    - Capital Outlay, miscellaneous, 1996-1999 (Box 165)
    - Capital Projects, 1994-1999 (Box 165)
    - Central Bank, 1998-2000; 6 folders (Box 165)
    - Child Care, 1988-1995 (Box 165)
    - Commencements, 1993-1995 (Box 165)
    - Compensation
      - Administrative Salaries, miscellaneous, 1990-1997; 5 folders (Box 166)
      - Deferred, 1981-1993 (Box 166)
      - Salary Increase Program, 1992-1998; 4 folders (Box 166)
      - Salary Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 166)
    - Computers -- Business and Networking, 1989-1997; 3 folders (Box 167)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1992-1999; 4 folders (Box 167)
    - Dearborn, UM, 1992-1995 (Box 167)
    - Delegation of Authority
      - 1995-1999 (Box 167)
        (7 folders)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 168)
    - Development -- New Capital Campaign, 1992-1998; 6 folders (Box 168)
    - Disabilities Information, 1992 (Box 168)
    - Diversity -- Business and Finance, 2000 (Box 168)
    - Engineering, College of, 1992-1998; 2 folders (Box 168)
    - Executive Car Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 168)
    - Financial Analysis, Office of, 1993-1995 (Box 169)
    - Financial Operations, 1992-1999 (Box 169)
      (8 folders)
    - Financing Buildings
      - Capital Bonds Proposals, 1971-1994; 2 folders (Box 169)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973-1991; 3 folders (Box 170)
    - Flint, U of M, Autoworld, 1994-1998; 3 folders (Box 170)
    - Gifts -- Current, 1992-1998 (Box 170)
    - Governor's Task Force on Venture Capital, 1995-1998 (Box 170)
    - Health Alliance, 1994 (Box 170)
    - Housing, Miscellaneous, 1992-1999; 5 folders (Box 170)
    - Human Resources
      - Miscellaneous, 1992-1997; 3 folders (Box 171)
      - Employment Open and Wanted, 1996-1999; 4 folders (Box 171)
      - Executive Director of Human Resources and Affirmative Action -- Search, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 171)
      - Jobnet, 1989-1994 (Box 171)
      - Human Resources Review Committee, 1992 (Box 171)
    - Indirect Cost
      - 1981-June1992, 4 folders (Box 171)
      - July 1992-December 1992, 2 folders (Box 172)
    - Information Technology Division (ITD), 1997-1998; 4 folders (Box 172)
    - Insurance (Risk Management)
      - Miscellaneous, 1996-1999; 3 folders (Box 172)
      - Veritas
        - 1998, 2 folders (Box 172)
        - 1996-1997, 7 folders (Box 173)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1992-1998; 6 folders (Box 173)
    - Investment Office, miscellaneous, 1992-1999; 6 folders (Box 174)
    - Investments
      - Contacts, 1998-1999 (Box 174)
      - Investment Managers
        - 1997-1998, 3 folders (Box 174)
        - 1994-1996, 4 folders (Box 175)
      - Policies and Procedures, 1992-1998; 4 folders (Box 175)
      - Rating Agencies, 1992-1999; 2 folders (Box 175)
      - Reports to Regents
        - 1993-1998, 13 folders (Box 176)
        - 1992 (Box 177)
    - Literature Science and the Arts, College of, 1994-1998; 2 folders (Box 177)
    - Medical Affairs, Executive Vice President/Provost for, 1992-1998 (Box 177)
    - Medical School, 1992-1999; 5 folders (Box 177)
    - Michigan, State of
      - Miscellaneous, 1997-1999; 2 folders (Box 177)
      - Budget, 1992-1999; 5 folders (Box 177)
      - Use and Financing Statements, 1992-1998; 2 folders (Box 178)
    - Musical Society, 1992-1994 (Box 178)
    - Name / Address Data Base, 1994-1995 (Box 178)
    - Organization, University, 1992-1998; 2 folders (Box 178)
    - North Campus Waste Management and Transfer Facility, 1991-1994 (Box 178)
    - Parking, miscellaneous, 1996-1999; 3 folders (Box 178)
    - Payroll, 1991-1998 (Box 178)
    - Perceptions of the Work Environment Survey, 1994-1995 (Box 178)
    - Plant, miscellaneous, 1992-1998; 3 folders (Box 179)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1992-1998; 9 folders (Box 179)
    - Political, 1995; 3 folders (Box 180)
    - President's New Century Fund, 1997 (Box 180)
    - Purchasing, 1992-1999; 4 folders (Box 180)
    - Regents
      - Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 180)
      - By-Laws, 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 180)
      - Communications
        - June-December 2000, 2 folders (Box 180)
        - January-May 2000, 3 folders (Box 181)
      - Regent Deane Baker (Box 181)
      - 1972-1994, 3 folders (Box 181)
      - Regent Paul Brown, 1972-1994 (Box 181)
      - Regent Philip H. Power, 1987-2001; 5 folders (Box 181)
      - Regent Thomas A. Roach, 1974-1990 (Box 181)
      - Regent Veronica L. Smith, 1985-1993 (Box 181)
      - Regent Nellie M. Varner, 1981-1996 (Box 181)
      - Regent James L. Waters, 1971-1994 (Box 181)
    - Research, Miscellaneous, 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box 182)
    - Retirement Housing, Faculty (Harold Johnson), 1974-1990 (Box 182)
    - Safety -- Regental Ordinance, 1991-1995; 2 folders (Box 182)
    - Shared Service Organization, 1998-2000; 2 folders (Box 182)
    - Staff Benefits
      - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996; 2 folders (Box 182)
      - Regents Communications, 1972-1989 (Box 182)
      - Retirement
        - 1992, 2 folders (Box 182)
        - 1993-2001, 4 folders (Box 183)
        - TIAA/CREF, 1995-2001 (Box 183)
      - Review, 2001-2002 (Box 184)
      - Survey, 2000-2003 (Box 184)
      - Early Retirement, 1985-2000 (Box 184)
      - Group Life Insurance, 2000-2001 (Box 184)
      - Integrated Disability Management Program, 1997-2001 (Box 184)
      - Long Term Disability, 1992-2000 (Box 184)
      - Medicare Reimbursement, 2001 (Box 184)
      - Prescription Drugs, Pharmaceuticals, 2000-2002; 2 folders (Box 184)
    - Students, Problems, 1999-2002 (Box 184)
    - Student Publications, Board for, 1992-2001 (Box 184)
    - Sugar Island, Miscellaneous, 1967-1993 (Box 184)
      (see also: Osborn)
    - Sustainable Environment, 1999-2003; 3 folders (Box 184)
    - Strategic Data Planning Project, 1993-1996; 3 folders (Box 185)
    - Student Affairs, Office of, 1996-1999 (Box 185)
      (was Student Services)
    - Taubman, A. Alfred, Consultant, 1989-1991; 3 folders (Box 185)
    - Technology Management Office
      - 1996-1999, 4 folders (Box 185)
      - 1993-1995, 8 folders (Box 186)
    - Toyota, 2000-2001 (Box 186)
    - Transportation, 1992-1995; 1997-2001; 4 folders (Box 186)
    - Travel and Reimbursement
      - 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box 186)
      - 1992-1998, 3 folders (Box 187)
    - Treasurer / AVP, 1999-2001 (Box 187)
    - Treasurer's Office, 1996-2001 (Box 187)
    - Undergraduate Commissions, 2001 (Box 187)
    - University Relations, 1994-1995; 1997-2001; 4 folders (Box 187)
    - Utilities
      - 2000-2001, 4 folders (Box 187)
      - 1999, 2 folders (Box 188)
    - Washington -- Residential Study Center, 1990-1991 (Box 188)
    - White, B. Joseph(Interim President), 2001 (Box 188)
    - Willow Run
      - Air Pollution, 1967-1968 (Box 188)
      - Trade Port, 1994-1999 (Box 188)
    - Women, President's Task Force on Violence Against, 1998 (Box 188)
    - Women's Agenda, 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box 188)
    - Women's Leadership Program
      - Conferences, Workshop, Etc.(Bryn Mawr Summer Institute), 1985-1991 (Box 188)
      - 1994-1997, 2 folders (Box 188)
    - Zell, Sam, 1999-2001; 7 folders (Box 189)
  - , ), 1960-2006; 2000-2003
    The subseries was accessioned by the Bentley in 2008. Records included in this accession primarily come from the later years of Robert Kasdin's time as CFO, with a few assorted files from earlier time periods, as well as projects that continued into the beginning of Timothy Slottow's term. Significant sections include files regarding the audit, budget, Chief Information Officer, and human resources.
    - Treasurer's Office-SWAPS, Major Capital Projects, 1993 (Box 205)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2028 ]
    - Liquidity & Mixed vs. Variable, circa 2000 (Box 205)
    - Annual Report of Investments, 1999-2000 (Box 205)
    - Business Office Recharge, circa, 2000 (Box 205)
    - Rating Agencies, 2002 (Box 205)
    - Regents of the University of Michigan General Revenue Bonds Series, 2002 (Box 205)
    - Commercial Paper/Cashflows Arbitage, circa, 2000 (Box 205)
    - Moody's Investors Service, 1999 (Box 205)
    - Recharges, circa, 2000 (Box 205)
    - Refinancing/Refunding, circa 2000 (Box 205)
    - North Hall Blueprint, 2001 (Folder 1)
    - Academic Affairs: Provost, 2002-2003 (Box 5)
    - Audit
      - Accenture, 2002-2003 (Folder 1)
      - Auditor General Dearborn, 2002 (Box 206)
      - Auditor General Flint, 2002 (Box 206)
      - Internal Reports, 2002 (Box 206)
      - Internal reports, 2003 (Box 206)
      - Auditor General -- General Fund, 2003 (Box 206)
      - Internal Discussions, 2003 (Box 206)
      - Outside Auditors, 2001-2003 (Box 206)
      - Price Waterhouse Coopers, 2003 (Box 206)
      - Price Waterhouse Coopers, 2002; 2 folders (Box 206)
      - Regent Communications, 2001-2003 (Box 206)
    - Budget
      - CFO Area, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 206)
      - July Budget Presentation, 2002 (Box 207)
      - Misc., 2002 (Box 207)
      - Misc., 2003 (Box 207)
      - Regent Communications, 2002-2003 (Box 207)
      - Michigan Appropriations, 2002-2003 (Box 207)
    - Price Waterhouse Coopers UMHHCS Financial Review and Operation Performance, 2000 (Box 207)
    - Ambulatory Care Services Strategic Plan, 2004 (Box 207)
    - HRAA Chief Human Resources Officer Search, 2003 (Box 207)
    - Business Administration, School of -- Miscellaneous, 2001-2003 (Box 207)
    - Communications, VP for (Box 208)
      - Miscellaneous, 2000-2003 (Box 208)
      - Newsclippings, Miscellaneous, 2000-2003 (Box 208)
      - Michigan Television Center, 1970-73 (Box 208)
    - Development
      - Office, 2002-2003 (Box 208)
      - Donors, 2002-2003 (Box 208)
      - Gifts, 2002-2003 (Box 208)
    - Business & Finance Management Institute, 1994 (Box 208)
    - Sponsored Programs Financial Report Tracking Project, Data Cleanup and Analysis Report, 2001 (Box 208)
    - Fiscal Year General Fund Initiatives, 2002 (Box 208)
    - Sponsored Programs Implementation Plan, 2002 (Box 209)
    - Strategic Planning Steering Committee, 1999 (Box 209)
    - M-Pathways -- HRMS Final Report, 2000 (Box 209)
    - Utilities Management: A Comprehensive Program, 2000 (Box 209)
    - Investment Advisory Committee, 2000-2002; 5 folders (Box 209)
    - 1960-2006, 2000-2003 (Box 209)
    - Utilities, Budgets & Rates Review/Chilled Water Proposal (Box 210)
    - UM Dearborn, Ford Training and Development Center, 2002 (Box 210)
    - HRAA
      - HR & Benefits, Business Plan & Operations Recharge (Box 210)
      - Initiative Detail (Box 210)
    - CIO (Chief Investment Officer)
      - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 210)
      - Endowment Performance, 2002-2003 (Box 210)
      - Long Term Portfolio, 2003 (Box 210)
      - Policies and Procedures, 2002 (Box 210)
      - Rating Agency, 2001-2003; 3 folders (Box 211)
      - University Investment Pools, 2002 (Box 211)
    - Exterior Elements Design Review Committee, 1967-1998 (Box 211)
    - Facilities and Operations
      - AVP Misc., 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 211)
      - Lock/Unlock, 2003 (Box 211)
      - Occupational Safety & Environmental Health, 1996-2003 (Box 211)
      - Parking & Transportation, Misc., 1993-2003 (Box 212)
      - Parking & Transportation -- VIP Permits, 1994-1995 (Box 212)
      - Plant, 1960-2003 (Box 212)
    - Human Resources
      - Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 212)
      - Classification System Management Project, 2001-2003 (Box 212)
      - Compensation -- Salary Increase Program, 2002-2003 (Box 212)
      - Compensation Study, 2002-2003 (Box 212)
      - Global Challenges, 2002 (Box 212)
      - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003 (Box 212)
      - Stewardship, 2001-2002 (Box 212)
      - Labor Relations-AFSCME, 2003 (Box 212)
      - Labor Relations-Engineers, 2002 (Box 212)
      - Staff Benefits, Committee on, 2002-2003 (Box 213)
      - Staff Benefits -- Miscellaneous (Box 213)
      - Staff Benefits -- Other Post Retirement, 2002-2003 (Box 213)
      - Staff Benefits-Prescription Drugs/ Pharmaceuticals, 2002-2003 (Box 213)
      - Staff Benefits -- Retirement, 2003 (Box 213)
    - Internal Bank (Box 213)
    - Life Sciences, 2002-2003; .ppt file (Box 213)
    - Michigan Admin. Information Services (MAIS) -- Miscellaneous, 2003; 2 folders (Box 213)
    - AVPF: Purchasing -- Conflict of Interest, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 214)
    - Law School -- W.W. Cook Trust, 2003 (Box 214)
    - Michigan Highway Testing Lab, 1964-1969 (Box 214)
    - Musical Society, 2002-2003 (Box 214)
    - Natural Resources, School of, 2002-2003 (Box 214)
    - Packard Hanger -- Miscellaneous, 1988-2006 (Box 214)
    - Pollard Medical Research Center, 1977-1983 (Box 214)
    - Printing Services, 1982-1983 (Box 214)
    - North Campus Religious Center (Box 214)
    - RAK Speeches, 2001-2003 (Box 214)
    - Research (Box 215)
      - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003; 2 folders (Box 215)
      - Tech Transfer Misc, 2001-2003 (Box 215)
    - Spiritual Life Center -- Proposed, 2002 (Box 215)
- Supplemental Files
  - 1957-2004
    The Supplemental Files, 1957-2001 (bulk 1993-2003), comprise several smaller sets of topical files maintained outside of the general files, related to only a few main topics. The bulk of the files date from the tenures of Farris Womack and Robert Kasdin. One issue of particular significance from Kasdin's term was the reorganization of the university's hospital and medical center in the mid-1990s, which is documented in a series of Hospital supplemental files.
    - Facilities and Operations, 1957-1997
      - Miscellaneous Renovations, 1975-1997; 3 folders (Box 190)
      - A & D Remodeling, 1968-1979 (Box 190)
      - Astronomy -- Proposal for Undergraduate Astronomy Center, 1971 (Box 190)
      - Benz Building, 1972-1984 (Box 190)
      - Biomedical Research, 1968 (Box 190)
      - Center for Human Growth and Development, 1966-1969 (Box 190)
      - Food Stores -- New, 1957-1968 (Box 190)
      - Henderson House, 1980-1981 (Box 190)
      - Laundry, 1956-1978 (Box 190)
      - University Motel, 1972-1974 (Box 190)
      - University Terrace, 1986-1987 (Box 190)
      - Upjohn Center for Clinical Pharmacology, 1966-1970 (Box 190)
      - Water Pollution Control Laboratory (HEW), 1961-1973 (Box 190)